Christine Pattee Lesbiana Collection ca. 1970-2000 GLBTQ.2011.02
GLBTQ Archives, Central Connecticut State University
- Series I: Christine Pattee Papers
  - Veteran Feminists of America Celbrates the 30th anniversary of teh Women's Liberation Movement and honors Founders and Activitists; (program booklet); December 13, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Official Souvenir game Program 1998 Nike/WBCA High School All-America Game; April 4, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - War Widow television program (information), undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Mirabella (magazine), March 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Program Book, Feminist Expo 2000, March 31, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Child-In flyer: "Monday May, 11, Beineke Plaza", undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Bowen-Peters Dancers 1980 Calendar (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Blaisdell, Virginia, Dimow, Joan, Living here: New Haven, n.d. (photocopy of 2 pages); Original in book collection., undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Margie Adams concert information, July 16, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Women's Music For Everyone, 1980-1981, Planning Information (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Women's Music For Everyone: Poster, Mailer plans, articles, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Women's Music For Everyone, Letter and Mailing List, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New England Women's Musical Retreat, background material, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New England Women's Musical Retreat, information on 1981 retreat, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - First New England Women's Musical Retreat Financial Report, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - New England Women's Retreat, 1981 photo contact sheet (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Second New England Women's Musical Retreat, 1982 Bookeeping and letter (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - NEWMR 1983 plans (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - North East Women's Musical Retreat programs 1981, 1982-1984, 1987, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Musica Femina, 1985 informational sheet on spring tour of duet Janna MacAuslan and Kristan Aspen (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Diedre McCalla program booklet, 1989, presented by Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - LABRYS brochure on musical group comprised of Elena Jordan and Patricia Lyons, n.d., undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Black Binder planning book for Women's Music For Everyone, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Series II: Records of the North Eastern Women’s Musical Retreat, from Deedy Breed
  - NEWMR Programs 1982, 1987, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NEWMR Programs: 1991, 1993, 1997, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Breetz & Thorn, Attorneys at Law, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Federal and state taxes, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Minutes of Cluster vs. NEWMR (model); correspondence, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Conn. Dept of Labor employer status 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Federal taxes, 1990-1991
  - Income taxes 1990-2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Budget 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Contract between NEWMR and Circle of Voices, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - NEWMR Membership, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - CPA report on Branford Land Trust, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Computer purchase 1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - First Constitution Bank statements, correspondence. 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer's Notes, 1988, 1991, 1992, Finance Committee minutes; Philosophy of Land Use (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Membership list and letter, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Shipman & Goodwin, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors 1988-1995 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Webster Bank CD 1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Minutes 1995-1998 (Box 11)
  - Survey (no date), undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Festival Receipts 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Membership Brochures (typeset originals), undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Master flyer 1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Newsletter, Certificate of Incorporation, By Laws, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - NEWMR vx. Greatan Holman 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Festival Financials, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - New Haven Bank Statements 1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Charitable funds and forms 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Insurance Retreat 1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Final Meeting, 2000; tax return for 1999, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Dissolution papers; by laws 2000 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Expenses 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Bank Statements, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Dissolution of NEWMR, August 14, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Donation of treasury to Astraea September 18, 2002; Board minutes Sept. 29, 2001, 2001, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - CT Sales & Use Tax Returns 1988-1990; 1993, 1997, 1999, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - CPA reports for 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - NEWMR Reunion 2001 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - White Binder overview of planning and minutes, 1993-1998 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Blue Binder; Board of Directors Meetings 1988 – 1996 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Black Binder, NEWMR Corporate Minute Book (formal), 1988-2001 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Series III: Photographic Materials
  - NEWMR 2 at Lake of Isles. Boy Scout Camp, now part of Foxwoods. 25 sheets holding 250 color photographs. Photographs probably taken by Loretta Wrobel C. Pattee, undated (Box 12, Oversize 1)
  - NEWMR slides taken by Kate Sherwood, 74 color slides, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - NEWMR prints taken mostly by Cary Chapin—333 black and white prints, 347 color prints and negatives, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NEWMR slides taken by Kate Sherwood, 136 color slides, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NEWMR 3: 3 sheets holding 30 black and white photographs, undated (Box 12, Oversize 2)
  - 9 sheets holding 145 color slides, 1990 – (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 2 large color photographs, NEWMR 1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 2 large photographs, Ten Mile River, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Photographs by H. Katz and others, mostly black and white., undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 2 Photographs of Gay Pride parade, Hartford, June 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Contact sheet (NEWMR), undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 16 color slides in a yellow kodak carton, 1977; 1978; 1983; undated (Box 12, Carton 3)
  - 18 color slides in a yellow kodak carton, undated (Box 12, Carton 4)
  - 13 color slides in a yellow kodak carton, 1982; 1987; 1988; undated (Box 12, Carton 5)
  - 18 color slides in a blue plastic carton, 1975; undated (Box 12, Carton 6)
  - 23 color slides in a blue plastic carton, 1974; 1975; undated (Box 12, Carton 7)
  - 35 color slides in a navy blue carton, 1987 (Box 12, Carton 8)
  - 25 color slides in a navy blue carton, 1987 (Box 12, Carton 9)
  - 18 color slides in a navy blue carton, 1987 (Box 12, Carton 10)
  - NEWMR plastic box of slides, undated (Box 12, Carton 11)
    plastic box 1. 29 slides
    plastic box 2. 27 slides
    plastic box 3. 25 slides
    plastic box 4. 18 slides
    plastic box 5. 19 slides
  - NEWMR plastic box of slides, undated (Box 12, Carton 12)
  - NEWMR plastic box of slides, undated (Box 12, Carton 13)
  - NEWMR plastic box of slides, undated (Box 12, Carton 14)
  - NEWMR plastic box of slides, undated (Box 12, Carton 15)
  - Clarice, NEWMR II: 11 color slides, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Susan McShane’s accessibility: 18 slides in a red carton, undated (Box 12)
  - NEWMR, pre-Friday orientation/registration/rain: white plastic box 1; 48 color slides, undated (Box 12, Carton 1)
  - NEWMR workshops, Helen Space, crafts, health building, political tent, women of color tent, central information and orientation, white plastic box 2; 46 color slides, undated (Box 12, Carton 2)
  - NEWMR Lake of Isles: Box 1: 33 color slides, 1988 (Box 13)
  - NEWMR Lake of Isles: Box 2: 32 color slides, 1988 (Box 13)
  - NEWMR Lake of Isles: Box 3: 36 color slides, 1988 (Box 13)
  - NEWMR Lake of Isles: Box 4: 21 color slides, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Lynch/Vanderhoff, plastic box 1: 27 color slides, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Lynch/Vanderhoff, plastic box 2: 30 color slides, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Lynch/ Vanderhoff, plastic box 3: 31 color slides, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Lynch/ Vanderhoff, plastic box 4: 36 color slides, undated (Box 13)
  - Rhode Island camp, plastic box, 25 color slides, 1982; 1983; 1987; undated (Box 13)
- Series IV: T-Shirts
  - Green; Logo Hartford Gay and Lesbian Health Collective, Celebrating 25 years (n.d.), undated
  - Pink; New England Women's Musical Retreat, 1981
  - Blue; New England Women's Musical Retreat, 1981
  - Purple; New England Women's Musical Retreat, 1982
  - Gray; North East Women's Musical Retreat, 1998
  - Pink; North East Women's Musical Retreat, 1990
  - White; North East Women's Musical Retreat, 1991
  - Red; North East Women's Musical Retreat, 1988
  - Blue; Susan B. Anthony, “Failure is impossible!” made by FERNE n.d., undated
  - White; Hartford Gay and Lesbian Health Collective, Be Well Be Yourself, n.d., undated
  - White; Hartford Gay and Lesbian Health Collective, four triangles with letters, n.d., undated
  - White; The National Lesbian and Gay Health Association, purple triangle with letters, n.d., undated
  - White; The Names Project Purple, n.d., undated
  - White; Connecticut Lesbian/Gay/Bisexual Pride Day June 19, 1993
  - White; It's Not Just a Phase, “Don't Panic”, 1992
  - Purple; New Haven Women's Liberation Movement, n.d., undated
- Series V: Realia and Miscellaneous
  - Box of political buttons, 1970's - 1980's (Box 13, Carton 2)
  - Box of political buttons, 1970's - 1980's (Box 13, Carton 1)
  - 3 name tags; 1 belonging to Deedy Breed, 1 belonging to Christine Pattee, and 1 belonging to Terry Guzauckas, undated (Box 14)
  - Package of approximately 100 NEWMR membership cards, undated (Box 14)
  - Stamp, For Deposit Only N.E.M.A.R., undated (Box 14)
  - Checkbook, Fleet Bank, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Checkbook, Cape Cod 5, 2000-2002 (Box 14)
  - Cancelled bankbook, Cape Cod 5, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Photos and memories of a young dyke: two photo albums/memoirs with accompanying explanation., undated
  - Roosevelt School, Ossining, New York, 1953-1955
  - Camp Wiquanuppek, Bear Mountain, New York, 1957
  - Circular wood plague 15 cm diameter carved; Final NEWMR Logo by Kathy Lewis, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Circular wood plaque 16 cm in diameter; First NEWMR Logo, carved by Mei Mei Sanford, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Feminist posters, 1980's (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Typeset slogans for Women's Liberation (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bumper sticker, "A woman's place is everyplace" (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Women's Sports calendar, 1981, with notes by C. Pattee (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Women's Music for EveryOne poster and ticket order form mailer, 1981 (Box 14)